We'll call it over the
Speaker's good to meet in my city council for Monday, June 17th, 2024.
Public input and scheduled personal passes.
We have none.
Three kinds list.
Most approve.
Hi.
Thank you.
Four kinds list for any of you.
Concrete.
Most approve.
Second.
East.
Hi.
Joe.
I'm staying.
Hi.
Five minutes from the May 20th, 2024.
May 21st, 2024.
Special meeting.
And June 3rd, 2024.
Regular meeting.
Motion no proof.
Second.
Jones.
Fifth.
Parker.
Contract member number one.
For annual six month on call of concrete.
Repair.
C23-58.
With Haskell.
Fabrications.
Scott.
Construction.
Concrete.
Documents.
This is the same one.
Brian.
Just talk about.
The English you would.
Second.
Jones.
Fifth.
Second.
Hi.
Remember, I'm a vendor standing with the Auto County E901 Trust Authority for this
by Services for the first week of your 24 or 25 chief general.
Yes, this is approving an annual contract with E901, with County Sheriff's Office
for the A7375 dollars a month.
So this is the E911, but they provide 5,000 monthly payment to us for 60,000 a year and then on top of that they have a $121,000
long javiti stipend for dispatchers to make those criteria.
So total of 74,000, 532 dollars by dispatching 2,000.
Does this pretty much the same last year?
Is there different dates?
Yes.
Jones?
Hi.
E7?
Okay.
In contract auto kind of sheriff's office for dispatch services for fiscal year 24 or 25,
this is the same agreement from last year's that they did.
I'll make a motion to group.
Hi.
Drillful.
Jones.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
In FPR solutions, coalitions, management, consulting agreement with the CVS,
joint agreement for prescription benefit portion of the employee health insurance plan, authorized
entrance to the manager's side.
Sit down.
This is the prescription piece that goes with our health plan for insurance for companies.
So, where we've been a member of this coalition since 2017 and because there are several members in the coalition, it allows us to get our prescriptions that allow lesser price.
So, same as it was before this.
It was just renewing it.
Motion to group.
Second.
Jones.
Hi.
Hitman.
Don't vote.
Hi.
12 amendment to the professional services agreement.
Garver for construction and administration services for the new airport kind of.
She banishes.
We are counsel.
Good news.
I don't worry more money.
That's really important.
This is a.
The engineering contract with Garver just the next phase.
As part of the original budget.
It's just signing in.
They've overseen construction and the next phase of construction.
This is just the contract that extends to the next phase.
Motion to approve.
Take it.
So cool.
Hi.
Eastern.
Jones.
Hitman.
Hi.
Thank you.
13.
New business of any which is the post.
Thank you.
14 staff reports 15 mayor and council community announcements. This was a good job. Our CVB office for the main game
Got another one behind this and now we're looking forward to the best for that
You got dinner on a street first one those coming up so a lot of stuff going on downtown with our CVB
So we appreciate them pulling out off with the CVB
Probably with the eight man and everything went well 16 city manager's communication
So now some team this may what I'll be continued from council chambers to the staff from the purpose of executive set